https://www.rashmian.com/privacy-notice

View All Brands
A&D MedicalEnergizerInfapowerLogic3PowertravellerSilent WitnessTexas InstrumentsWahl
Hair Care
Personal Protective Equipment (PPE)
Privacy Notice
Rashmian Ltd takes your privacy rights as a customer seriously. Any personal information provided to rashmian.com is used solely by Rashmian Ltd, Unit J Braintree Industrial Estate, Braintree Road, Ruislip, Middlesex, HA4 0EJ. This statement describes the information which we may ask for, and the ways in which we may use that information.For clarity, Rashmian may be both data controller and data processor for your personal data under certain circumstances.We must advise that this policy is subject to change, so please check our website on a regular basis for any further changes.Data Protection law will change on 25 May 2018 This Privacy Notice sets out your rights under the new laws. Who are we?Rashmian is a distributor of consumer electronics based in London. Rashmian have a registered office at Unit J, Braintree Industrial Estate, Braintree Road, Ruislip, HA4 0EJ and company number 1280301. How the law protects you?Data protection laws state that we are only able to process personal data if we have valid reasons to do so. The reasons we process your personal data include, but not limited to, your consent, performance of a contract, billing and to contact you.The information we collect and how we use it:In order to monitor the performance of our site we collect the following information:An IP address to monitor site traffic and volume A session ID to uniquely identify you on our siteWhen registering on our website and/or to fulfil any orders placed with rashmian.com we collect the following details:NameInvoice AddressShipping AddressTelephone NumberEmail AddressBuying Preferences to aid navigation and inform them of offers if they so requestCard/bank details may be taken over the phone in order to process your order. Additionally we also collect information from you when you sign up, enter a competition, promotion or survey or when you inform us of any other matter.If you provide us with personal data about a third party (for example when registering a domain on their behalf), you warrant that you have obtained the express consent from the third party for the disclosure and use of their personal data.We collect information on your use of the site about you which does not identify you personally to provide you with information, products and promotions, which may interest to you. This information is collected and stored as a "cookie" on your computer"s hard drive for record-keeping purposes. The use of cookies is standard and can enhance your use of a site by helping us to identify your personal areas of interest. Most web browsers allow you to disable the automatic acceptance of cookies if you so wish. However you may not be able to take advantage of all the features of our website if you do so.Retention periodsWe will keep your personal data for the duration of the period you are a customer of Rashmian. We shall retain your data only for as long as necessary in accordance with applicable laws.On the closure of your account, we may keep your data for up to 7 years after you have cancelled your services with us. We may not be able to delete your data before this time due to our legal and/or accountancy obligations. We may also keep it for research or statistical purposes. We assure you that your personal data shall only be used for these purposes stated herein.Who has access to your personal data?Office/Warehouse AdministratorsWebsite DevelopersIT Administrators AuditorsInformation provided to third parties:This website contains links to sites over which we have no control. These sites may have information practices, which differ from those, described here and you are advised to consult the privacy notices of those sites before giving any personal information.Third PartiesFor the avoidance of doubt, we do not and never shall sell your personal data to third parties for marketing or advertising purposes.We may pass your personal data to third parties for the provision of services on our behalf (for example prcoessing your payment or using a mail system to send newsletters). However, we will only ever share information about you that is necessary to provide the service and we have specific contracts in place, which ensure your personal data is secure.We may share your information if we are acquired by a third party and therefore your data will be deemed an asset of the business. In these circumstances, we may disclose your personal data to the prospective buyer of our business, subject to both parties entering into appropriate confidentiality undertakings. Similarly, we may share your personal data if we are under a duty to disclose data in order to comply with any legal obligation or to protect the rights, property, or safety of Rashmian, our customers, or others. This includes but is not limited to exchanging information with other companies and organisations for the purposes of fraud protection, credit risk reduction and dispute policies. However, we will take steps with the aim of ensuring that your privacy rights continue to be protected.Security:When you place orders or access your account information, we offer the use of a secure server. The secure server software (SSL) encrypts all information you input before it is sent to us. Furthermore, as required by the UK Data Protection Legislation, we follow strict security procedures in the storage and disclosure of information which you have given us, to prevent unauthorised access. Our security procedures mean that we may occasionally request proof of identity before we are able to disclose sensitive information to you.If you do not wish to receive correspondence from us:We will not contact you for marketing purposes unless you have given us your prior consent. You may decide you do not wish to receive e-mails, newsletters or information about promotions or competitions from us. If you would rather not then please do not tick the appropriate box when you register with us, or alternatively click the "unsubscribe" link at the bottom of the newsletters. Alternatively you can email or ring us requesting deletion of your account.  Where do we store your personal data?All information you provide to us is stored on our secured servers. The server is only accessible by authorised Rashmian personnel. As the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure, we cannot guarantee the security of your data transmitted to our site and any transmission is at your own risk. Once we have received your information, we will use strict procedures and security features to try to prevent unauthorised access.Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password which enables you to access certain parts of our website, you are responsible for keeping the password confidential. We ask you not to share a password with anyone.
Welcome to Rashmian
We are wholesalers and distributors of consumer electronics. This is a Trade Only website, and resellers must register and log-in to view prices.
Please click here to create an Account
Login
SubmitForgot password?
Universal Sport Armband for your Mobile Devices - Black/Grey £108.75
5 x
Ares Desk LED Lamp with Wireless Charging Pad & Clock - Black £131.25
55 x
Disney Frozen II Elsa Childrens Clock with Night Light £695.75
12 x
Super Mario Childrens Clock with Night Light £151.80
5 x
Ladies Cream Leather Strap Rose Gold Case And Dial 50M Watch £70.25
3 x
Ladies Solar Stainless Steel Bracelet Pink Dial 50M Watch £44.61
Disney Frozen II Bilingual Educational Laptop with 124 Activites £36.40
20 x
Travel Adaptor UK to Europe (Carded) £12.00
View Cart
What's new?
Mens Urban Dress Watch with Sunray Dial & Black Leather Strap
Mens Easy Reader Watch with Gold-Tone Case & Brown Leather Strap
Lexibook JC598FZI3
Disney Frozen II Bilingual Educational Laptop with 124 Activites
Reseller Services : promote, order & sell our products. FTP Feed, Amazon FBA, and more...
RASHMIAN LIMITED Unit J, Braintree Industrial Estate, Braintree Road, Ruislip, Middlesex HA4 0EJ. England (UK)
RASHMIAN LIMITED Unit J, Braintree Industrial Estate, Braintree Road, Ruislip, Middlesex HA4 0EJ. England (UK)
Get the latest deals in your inbox!
Go
Incorrect email address Thank you for joining our mailing list
Copyright © 2020 Rashmian Ltd
